// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answer
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Citizenship provisions are enshrined in the constitution in",
        answer: "Part II, Articles 5-11",
        options: ["Part II",
            "Part II, Articles 5-11",
            "Part II, Articles 5-6",
            "Part I, Articles 5-11"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "2.	Details on how citizenship may be acquired and terminated are enumerated in:",
        answer: "The Citizenship Act, 1955", options: ["Part II of the Constitution",
            "The Citizenship Act, 1955",
            "Schedule I of the Constitution",
            "Various enactments by Parliament"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which of the following rights was described by Dr. B.R. Ambedkar as ‘The Heart and Soul of the Constitution’?",
        answer: "Right to Constitutional Remedies",
        options: ["Right of Freedom of Religion",
            "Right to Property",
            "Right to Equality",
            "Right to Constitutional Remedies"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "On whom does the Constitution confer special responsibility for the enforcement of Fundamental Rights?",
        answer: "Supreme Court",
        options: ["Parliament",
            "Supreme Court",
            "President",
            "State Legislature"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Under which Article of the Constitution are the Cultural and Educational Rights granted?",
        answer: "Article 29 and 30",
        options: ["Article 29 and 31",
            "Article 29 and 32",
            "Article 29 and 30",
            "Article 30 and 31"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "If an Indian citizen is denied a public office because of his religion, which of the following Fundamental Rights is denied to him?",
        answer: "Right Equality",
        options: ["Right to Freedom",
            "Right to Equality",
            "Right to Freedom of religion",
            "Right against Exploitation"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Prohibition of discrimination on grounds of religion etc. (Article 15 of the Constitution of India) is a Fundamental Right classifiable under:",
        answer: "The Right to Equality", options: ["The Right to Freedom of Religion",
            "The Right against Exploitation",
            "The Cultural and Educational Rights",
            "The Right to Equality"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Any dispute regarding the violation of Fundamental Rights can be presented:",
        answer: "Either in the Supreme Court or in the High Court",
        options: ["In the Supreme Court only",
            "In the High Court only",
            "Either in the Supreme Court or in the High Court",
            "First in the Supreme Court and then in the High Court"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Untouchability is abolished and its practice is punishable according to:",
        answer: "Article 17",
        options: ["Article 15",
            "Article 16",
            "Article 17",
            "Article 15(4)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is the minimum permissible age for employment in any factory or mine?",
        answer: "14 years",
        options: ["12 years",
            "14 years",
            "16 years",
            "18 years"
        ]
    }
]